Finding aid for the Roger Memos scripts LSC.2244
UCLA Library Special Collections
Roger Memos scripts
ca. 1994-2006
UCLA Library Special Collections
Memos, Roger C.
LSC.2244
17.2 linear feet (43 boxes)
Television producer Roger Memos is best known for his work on television talk shows. The collection consists of script files and occasional production information from the television talk shows Caryl and Marilyn: Real Friends, Donnie and Marie, The George and Alana Show, The Megan Mullally Show and The Suzanne Somers Show.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Roger Memos, 2007.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9974964523606533
Biography/History
Roger Memos worked on television talk shows including Caryl and Marilyn: Real Friends, Donnie and Marie, The George and Alana Show, The Megan Mullally Show and The Suzanne Somers Show.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of scripts files related to the career of television producer and clearance administrator Roger Memos. Included are script drafts and occasional production information representing television talk shows: Caryl and Marilyn: Real Friends, Donnie and Marie, The George and Alana Show, The Megan Mullally Show and The Suzanne Somers Show. Additionally there is a very small amount of background information about guests for The Suzanne Somers Show.
Organization and Arrangement
The collection is arranged in alphabetical order by project title.
Television producers and directors -- California -- Los Angeles -- Archives.; Memos, Roger C.
- Caryl and Marilyn: Real Friends
  - Caryl and Marilyn: Real Friends - shows 96008-96020 scripts and production information, 1996 May-Jun (Box 26)
    Scope and Content
    Guests include: Ron Popeil, David Carradine, Ed Begley, Barbara Billingsley, Florence Henderson, Thelma Houston, Julia Sweeney, Dennis Franz, Dr. Joyce Brothers, among others.
  - Caryl and Marilyn: Real Friends - shows 96021-96029; 96031-96045 scripts and production information, 1996 Jun-July (Box 27)
    Guests include: Tammy Faye Bakker, George Wallace, Eartha Kitt, Kathy Najimy, Phyllis Diller, among others
  - Caryl and Marilyn: Real Friends - shows 96042-96072 scripts and production information, 1996 July-Sep (Box 28)
    Guests include: Casey Kasem, Keith Hamilton Cobb, Eddie Ciprian, Weird Al, Joe Piscopo, Carnie Wilson, among others. No script for show 96068, only production information.
  - Caryl and Marilyn: Real Friends - shows 96073-96099 scripts and production information, 1996 Sep-Oct (Box 29)
    Guests include: Ricardo Montalban, Patty Hearst, Eartha Kitt, Little Richard, Wink Martindale, Brian McKNight, Andrea Martin, Lou Ferrigno, among others.
  - Caryl and Marilyn: Real Friends - shows 96100-96128 scripts and production information, 1996 Oct-Nov (Box 30)
    Guests include: Sherman Hemsley, Richard Simmons, Kris Jenner, Gabrielle Carteris, Tammy Faye [Bakker] Messner, Sheryl Lee Ralph, Tippi Hedren, Dweezil Zappa, Moon Unit Zappa, Deidre Hall, Amanda Bynes
  - Caryl and Marilyn: Real Friends - shows 96129-96162 scripts and production information, 1996 Nov-Jan 1997 (Box 31)
    Guests include: Mackenzie Phillips, Rodney Dangerfield, Casey Kasem, Dick Clark, Little Richard, Gavin Macleod, among others.
  - Caryl and Marilyn: Real Friends - shows 96163-96194 scripts and production information, 1997 Jan-Mar (Box 32)
    Guests include: Deepak Chopra,among others.
  - Caryl and Marilyn: Real Friends - shows 96195-96224 scripts and production information, 1997 Mar-Apr (Box 33)
    Guests include: Jackie Collins, Suzanne Somers, Erik Estrada, Vicki Lawrence, Shirley Jones, among others.
  - Caryl and Marilyn: Real Friends - shows 96225-96250 scripts and production information, 1997 Apr-May (Box 34)
    Guests include: Robert Guillaume, Tanya Tucker, Esther Williams, Dick Clark, Dick Van Patten, Art Linkletter, among others.
  - Caryl and Marilyn: Real Friends - shows 96251-96256 scripts and production, 1997 May (Box 35)
    Guests include: Dr. Demento, Wink Martindale, among others.
  - Caryl and Marilyn: Real Friends - talent grids, 1996-1997 (Box 35)
- Donny and Marie
  - Donny and Marie - test shows 1-8 scripts and production information, 1998 July-Aug (Box 6)
    Shows 00A-00H.
  - Donny and Marie - shows 1001-1006 scripts and production information, 1998 Sep (Box 6)
  - Donny and Marie - shows 1007-1025 scripts and production information, 1998 Sep-Oct (Box 7)
  - Donny and Marie - shows 1026-1044 scripts and production information, 1998 Oct-Nov (Box 8)
  - Donny and Marie - shows 1045-1064 scripts and production information, 1998 Nov-Dec (Box 9)
  - Donny and Marie - shows 1065-1088 scripts and production information, 1998 Dec-Jan 1999 (Box 10)
  - Donny and Marie - shows 1089-1110 scripts and production information, 1999 Jan-Feb (Box 11)
  - Donny and Marie - shows 1111-1117; 1121-1131 scripts and production information, 1999 Feb-Mar (Box 12)
  - Donny and Marie - shows 1132-1151 scripts and production information, 1999 Mar-Apr (Box 13)
  - Donny and Marie - shows 1152-1171 scripts and production information, 1999 Apr-May (Box 14)
  - Donny and Marie - shows 1172-1182; 2001-2008 scripts and production information, 1999 May-Sep (Box 15)
  - Donny and Marie - shows 2009-2025 scripts and production information, 1999 Sep-Oct (Box 16)
  - Donny and Marie - shows 2026-2043 scripts and production information, 1999 Oct-Nov (Box 17)
  - Donny and Marie - shows 2044-2060 scripts and production information, 1999 Nov-Dec (Box 18)
  - Donny and Marie - shows 2061-2076 scripts and production information, 1999 Dec-Jan 2000 (Box 19)
  - Donny and Marie - shows 2077-2093 scripts and production information, 2000 Jan-Feb (Box 20)
  - Donny and Marie - shows 2095-2108 scripts and production information, 2000 Feb (Box 21)
  - Donny and Marie - shows 2109-2125 scripts and production information, 2000 Feb-Mar (Box 22)
  - Donny and Marie - shows 2126-2143 scripts and production information, 2000 Mar-Apr (Box 23)
  - Donny and Marie - shows 2144-2160 scripts and production information, 2000 Apr-May (Box 24)
  - Donny and Marie - shows 2161-2177 scripts and production information, 2000 Apr-May (Box 25)
  - Donny and Marie - shows 2178-2180 scripts and production information, 2000 Apr (Box 26)
  - Donny and Marie - taped show index for seasons 1 and 2, 1998-2000 (Box 26)
  - Donny and Marie - Donny and Marie talent grids for season 2, 2000
- The George and Alana Show
  - George and Alana Show (The) - back up shows 1-5 production information, 1995 (Box 1)
  - George and Alana Show (The) - shows 101-122 production information, 1995 (Box 1)
  - George and Alana Show (The) - shows 139-140 scripts and production information, 1995 (Box 2)
    Guests include: Ivana Trump, Genie Francis, Jonathan Frakes, among others.
  - George and Alana Show (The) - shows 141-149 production information (Box 2)
  - George and Alana Show (The) - shows 150 and 154 scripts and production information (Box 2)
    Guests include: Phil Hartman, The Temptations, Stefanie Powers, Robert Wagner, among others.
  - George and Alana Show (The) - shows 151-153 and 156 production information (Box 2)
  - George and Alana Show (The) - shows 157-174 scripts and production information, 1995 (Box 3)
    Scope and Contents
    No scripts for shows 159-162, 164, 165, 167-169, 172-173 Guests include: Kim Cattrall, Lloyd Bridges, Soupy Sales, Betty White, Steve Harvey, Sheryl Lee Ralph, among others.
  - George and Alana Show (The) - shows 178-187 scripts and production information, 1996 (Box 3)
    No script for show 180. Guests include: Peggy Lipton, Claudia Schiffer, Beverly D'Angelo, Diane Ladd, Wayne Newton, Bill Maher, Timothy Busfield, George Wallace, James Cromwell, among others.
  - George and Alana Show (The) - shows 188-207 scripts and production information, 1996 (Box 4)
    Guests include: Andy Dick, Judy Collins, Lynda Carter, Claudia Schiffer, Brian McKnight, Tea Leoni, Jody Watley, Mickey Dolenz, George Segal, Charlie Sheen, among others.
  - George and Alana Show (The) - shows 208-221 scripts and production information, 1996 (Box 5)
    Guests include: Morgan Fairchild, Ann Margret, Bridget Fonda, Rod Steiger, Tate Donovan, Bonnie Hunt, Jewel, among others.
  - George and Alana Show (The) - shows 223-225, 228 scripts and production information (Box 5)
    Guests include: Hunter Tylo, Dan O'Brien, among others.
  - George and Alana Show (The) - segment producer's schedules, 1995-1996 (Box 6)
- The Megan Mullally Show
  - Megan Mullally Show (The) - Test Show 1 and 2 scripts, 2006 Aug (Box 42)
  - Megan Mullally Show (The) - Evergreen 1-5 scripts, 2006 Aug (Box 42)
  - Megan Mullally Show (The) - shows 1001-1016 scripts, 2006 Aug-Sep (Box 42)
  - Megan Mullally Show (The) - shows 1017-1027; 1029-1033 scripts, 2006 Sep (Box 43)
- The Suzanne Somers Show
  - Suzanne Somers Show (The) - launch shows 1-7 scripts and some background information, 1994 July (Box 35)
  - Suzanne Somers Show (The) - launch shows 7-12 scripts and some background research, 1994 July (Box 36)
  - Suzanne Somers Show (The) - shows 1001-1007 scripts and some background information, 1994 Aug (Box 36)
  - Suzanne Somers Show (The) - shows 1008-1021 scripts and some background information, 1994 Aug-Sep (Box 37)
  - Suzanne Somers Show (The) - shows 1022-1033 scripts and some background information, 1994 Sep-Oct (Box 38)
  - Suzanne Somers Show (The) - shows 1034-1042 scripts and some background information, 1994 Oct (Box 39)
  - Suzanne Somers Show (The) - shows 1044-1056 scripts and some background information, 1994 Oct-Nov (Box 40)
  - Suzanne Somers Show (The) - shows 1057-1065 scripts and some background information, 1994 Nov (Box 41)
- Background information for Gabrielle Carteris, Lou Ferrigno, Loretta Lynn, Ed O'Neil, Jason Stuart, and Jean Stuart, 1994 (Box 41)